Name: Kemi Bedeau

Address: Lp112 Main Road, Point Ligoure, Point Fortin

Phone Number: 312-4189

Date of Birth: 21st March 1995

Marital Status: Single

Mission Statement: To enhance my knowledge and understanding, and to gain experience in the world of work so that I may be able to apply my knowledge meaningfully, contributing not only to my general process, but also to the organization with which I work.

Qualifications:

1998-2000

Sarah's Preparatory

Clifton Hill, Point Fortin Full Certificate

2000-2007

Point Fortin A.S.J.A Primary

Bryce Road, Point Fortin Full Certificate

2007-2011

St. Joseph's Convent

San-Fernando

CXC General Proficiency

English A Grade 1

English B Grade 2

Mathematics Grade 3

French	Grade 2
Biology	Grade 2
Chemistry	Grade 3
Food and Nutrition	Grade 1
2013-2014	
Trinidad and Tobago Hospitality and Tourism Institute	(Currently Pursuing)
Hill Top Lane, Chaguaramas	Diploma in Baking and Pastry
Work Experience:	
2009-2010	
Feroza's Shopping, Point Fortin	
Holiday Job	
2010-2011	
Hair By Naomi, Point Fortin	
Holiday Job	
2011-2012	
Cashe's, Gulf City	
Holiday Job	
Interest and Activities	
Playing Tennis	
Playing the Piano	
Baking/Cooking	

References:

Ms. Denise Maloney(Secretary)

Atlantic LNG, Point Fortin

648-1043

Ms. Cynthia Lennon (Retired Principal)

Mahica, Point Fortin